A Guide to the Small Collections, 1912-2017
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
Small Collections, 1912-2017
The Edgar Cayce Foundation, Virginia Beach, Virginia
Coll. 5
0.8 Linear Feet 2 boxes
Small Collections include donations from A.R.E. members and A.R.E. staff of organizational and personal materials to the Edgar Cayce Foundation.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection open for research use.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by donor surname.
Scope and Contents
Includes artifacts, books, documents, ephemera, and photographs.
- Box 1
  - certificate, A.R.E. Life Membership [Mr. and Mrs. James Dixon], 1976; Folder 1:1
  - name badge, [Jim Dixon], 2006; Folder 1:2
  - framed photograph, [Cayce Hospital building], 2004; Folder 1:3
  - photographs, [James Dixon estate], 1930-2000; Folder 1:4
  - plaque, A.R.E. Board of Trustees Service Award [Jim Dixon], 2000; Folder 1:5
  - plaque, A.R.E. Survey Lecture Program Service Award] Jim Dixon, 2000; Folder 1:6
- Box 2
  - ephemera and photographs [Ed Foote], 1960-1982; Folder 2:1
  - Betty McCain reading and related correspondence [Ned Hauptner], 1963-2017; Folder 2:2
  - printer's block [Vaughn Shelton], 1945-1960; Folder 2:3
  - printer's block, political cartoon [Vaughan Shelton], 1945-1960; Folder 2:4
  - printer's block, political cartoon [Vaughan Shelton], 1945-1960; Folder 2:5
  - bible [Jeri Westmoreland], 1912; Folder 2:6
  - bible ephemera [Jeri Westmoreland], 1912-1956; Folder 2:7-2:8